//2,2,3,2,2,4
import 'package:sih_app/widgets/question.dart';

const List<Question> questions = [
  Question(
    question: 'Q1). A bank offers 5% compound interest calculated on half-yearly basis. A customer deposits Rs. 1600 each on 1st January and 1st July of a year. At the end of the year, the amount he would have gained by way of interest is : ',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 121',
      'b) 122',
      'c) 123',
      'd) 124',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q2). The difference between simple and compound interests compounded annually on a certain sum of money for 2 years at 4% per annum is Re. 1. The sum (in Rs.) is : ',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) 625',
      'b) 630',
      'c) 640',
      'd) 659',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q3). There is 60% increase in an amount in 6 years at simple interest. What will be the compound interest of Rs. 12,000 after 3 years at the same rate ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) 2160',
      'b) 3120',
      'c) 3972',
      'd) 6240',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q4). What is the difference between the compound interests on Rs. 5000 for 1 years at 4% per annum compounded yearly and half-yearly ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Rs. 2.04',
      'b) Rs. 3.06',
      'c) Rs. 4.80',
      'd) Rs. 8.30',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q5). The compound interest on Rs. 30,000 at 7% per annum is Rs. 4347. The period (in years) is :',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) 2',
      'b) 2.5',
      'c) 3',
      'd) 4',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: "Q6). Which of the following words is an antonym (opposite) of ' Eloquent '?",
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Inarticulate',
      'b) Fluent',
      'c) Voluble',
      'd) Loquacious',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: 'Q7). Fill in the blank : If I were you, I _____ consider the job offer seriously.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Ought',
      'b) Can',
      'c) Would',
      'd) Must',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: "Q8). Choose the synonym for the word 'Ardent' :",
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) Lukewarm',
      'b) Enthusiastic',
      'c) Apathetic',
      'd) Indifferent',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:"Q9). Complete the analogy: 'Ocean is to water as forest is to ______.' :",
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) Trees',
      'b) Leaves',
      'c) Soil',
      'd) Mountain',
    ],
  ),
    Question(
    question: '10. Identify the grammatically incorrect sentence :',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) She sings beautifully.',
      'b) They was late for the meeting.',
      'c) He reads books every evening.',
      'd) We have already eaten dinner.',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '11. Choose the word that best fits in the blank : His actions spoke ______ than his words.',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Lighter',
      'b) Less',
      'c) Louder',
      'd) Lesser',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '12. Which of the following is NOT a renewable source of energy ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Solar power',
      'b) Wind power',
      'c) Natural gas',
      'd) Hydroelectric power',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '13. What is the chemical symbol for the element oxygen ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) O',
      'b) Ox',
      'c) Om',
      'd) Oz',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '14. Who painted the famous artwork - Mona Lisa ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Vincent van Gogh',
      'b) Pablo Picasso',
      'c) Leonardo da Vinci',
      'd) Leonardo Di Caprio',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question:
        '15. Which artistic movement is known for its use of bright colors, bold shapes, and abstraction of reality ?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) Impressionism',
      'b) Cubism',
      'c) Surrealism',
      'd) Abstract Expressionism',
    ],
  ),
];